

ABOUT ME

Creative, hard working graphic designer with 1 year of experience in creating illustrations. During my spare time I like to create illustrations or ideas for commissions or posts. I have been making traditional art for 15 years and switched to digital recently. Interested in making / creating, stickers, posters and illustrations.

CONTACT

Address

29488 58th ave, Abbotsford, B.C.

Phone

778-551-0664

Email

littlebetul@gmail.com

Social Media

LittleBB

EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2019



Graphic Designer

Free time

During my spare time I make illustrations and logo ideas for my close friends and family about their business / company.

- Interact about their interests
- Creating logo / illustration

2021 - Present



Fraser Valley Regional Library

Tag Team

As a group of teens, we'd get together and with the best of our efforts to project a fun and energetic atmosphere. All while we assist and help prepare the programs provided from the library staff.

- Interact and formed bonds with children
- Decorating management

EDUCATION

2021 - 2022



Graphic Design Diploma

CDI College

2015 - 2019



Graduate Diploma

W.J. Mouat Secondary

SKILLS





